HANNAH G SWIFT

Nashville, TN 931-206-9405

hannahgswift@gmail.com https://github.com/hannahgswift

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT

Personable web developer who enjoys creating responsive, user-friendly applications. Excited about adding to my skill-set and growing as a developer. Recently spent 3 months in an intensive coding boot-camp, learning new and innovative ways to build products that deliver great user experiences.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, Ember.js, Git, GitHub, NPM, Node.js, Object Oriented Programming, Responsive Web Design. Familiar with Adonis.js, Postgres, React.js, Test Driven Development.

I don't have a language or skill you're looking for? That's okay, I can learn it.

EDUCATION

The Iron Yard - Nashville, TN - Front End Engineering - 2016 Austin Peay State University - Clarksville, TN - B.S. Public Relations - 2013

EXPERIENCE

Student in The Iron Yard's Intensive Front-End Engineering Program - 2016

- -Spent 60+ hours each week building web applications using Vanilla JavaScript and MVC Frameworks, both individually and as a part of a team
- -Worked in a team for final project where we built Kin, an app designed to simplify the process of finding reliable babysitters in your area

Photographer, Hannah Swift Photography, Nashville, TN 2012 - Present

- Built relationships and consulted with clients during pre and post production to meet their needs
- -Technically proficient in Nikon imaging products, film, lenses, filters, etc
- -Used Adobe Photoshop and Lightroom to cull and edit photos

Registrar, Gateway Medical Center, Clarksville, TN, Sep 2014 - June 2015

- -Check physician referrals and log diagnosis codes in patient's account
- -Verify insurance and authorizations/pre-certifications for scheduled outpatient appointments
- -Communicate with patients about their procedures and account balances

Content Creator, Ashraya Mission, Mussoorie, India, Jan 2014 - May 2014

- -Used Ashraya Mission social media accounts and online presence to raise awareness of their mission (bringing an end to modern-day slavery)
- -Took photographs and wrote copy for online fundraising campaigns
- -Built relationships with local community leaders in order to see where Ashraya could contribute to helping similar causes